Guide to the Western Americana Card Photograph File
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Unidentified Photographers, circa 1850-circa 1951; Series II; 359
  - Identified Locations
    This subseries is organized according to image content, initially in alphabetical order by geographical locations in the United States, first by states and therein by localities, then by locations in Canada and other countries, then by images with unidentified locations arranged according the subject in the image and chronologically therein.
    - Alabama
      - View of the corpse of an African American man, identified as Morris Slater (died 1896), also known as Railroad Bill, at Atmore, Alabama, 1896 Mar; 10.0 x 13.9 cm on mount 10.7 x 16.5 cm (Box 14)
        Manuscript inscription on verso: "'Railroad Bill' the notorious negro desperado"
    - Alaska
      - Muir Glacier
        - Ice floes near Muir Glacier, Alaska, circa 1890-1900; 14.0 x 20.7 cm on mount 14.1 x 20.8 cm (Box 14)
        - Ice in front of Muir Glacier, Alaska, circa 1890-1900; 14.0 x 20.7 cm on mount 14.1 x 20.8 cm (Box 14)
        - Ice pinnacles at end of Muir Glacier, Alaska, circa 1890-1900; 14.0 x 20.8 cm on mount 14.1 x 20.9 cm (Box 14)
        - Two men camping with Muir Glacier, Alaska, in the distance, circa 1890-1900; 14.0 x 20.5 cm on mount 14.1 x 20.6 cm (Box 14)
      - Sitka
        - Exterior of Saint Michael the Archangel Cathedral, Sitka, Alaska, circa 1880-1890; 15.5 x 9.7 cm on mount 25.4 x 20.3 cm (Box 14)
        - Madonna icon in the interior of Saint Michael the Archangel Cathedral, Sitka, Alaska, circa 1890-1900; 19.1 x 11.2 cm on mount 21.5 x 13.3 cm (Box 14)
      - Wrangell
        - Totem poles, Chief Kat-a-shan's house, Wrangell, Alaska, circa 1900; 11.8 x 9.2 cm on mount 15.8 x 12.0 cm (Box 14)
        - Totem poles at Wrangell, Alaska, circa 1900; 11.8 x 9.3 cm on mount 15.8 x 12.0 cm (Box 14)
      - Unidentified locations in Alaska
        - Indian village with totem poles, Alaska, circa 1890-1900; 13.8 x 20.8 cm on mount 13.9 x 20.9 cm (Box 14)
        - Men in front of a tent rooming house, Alaska, circa 1898; 11.6 x 16.6 cm, unmounted (Box 14)
        - View of a mountain along the inland passage to Alaska, circa 1900; 8.3 x 11.0 cm, unmounted (Box 14)
    - Arizona
      - Grand Canyon
        - View of the Grand Canyon, Arizona, circa 1900 (Box 14)
      - Havasupai Indian Reservation
        - Navajo Falls, Havasupai Indian Reservation, Arizona, 1907; 8.0 x 10.7 cm, unmounted (Box 14)
      - Phoenix
        - Carriages and palm trees in front of a brick building in Phoenix, Arizona, 1877; 2 photographic prints 12.0 x 17.2 cm on mounts 13.9 x 19.1 cm (Box 14)
      - Tucson
        - A distant view of Tucson, Arizona, circa 1870-1879; 5.8 x 9.5 cm on mount 6.4 x 10.1 cm (Box 14)
      - Walpi
        - View of the Hopi Indian pueblo at Walpi, Arizona, circa 1896; 7.8 x 9.9 cm on mount 8.9 x 11.0 cm (Box 14)
          Image number 124
      - Unidentified locations
        - American Indians attending an outdoor Roman Catholic mass under an arbor, circa 1900; 9.1 x 9.7 cm on mount 10.7 x 13.3 cm (Box 14)
        - Views of a pueblo and American Indians performing a dance, each progressively moving closer to the dancers, circa 1888; 3 photographic prints, 6.5 x 6.5 cm on mount 10.0 x 12.7 cm (Box 14)
          Three circular photographic prints, probably created by an Original Kodak or a No. 1 Kodak camera
    - California
      - Brookdale
        - Brook Room of the Brookdale Lodge in Brookdale, California, circa 1936; 8.7 x 27.5 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
      - Castle Rocks
        - Mount Shasta from Devil's Castle (Castle Rocks), California, 1866 Jul; 5.8 x 9.5 cm on mount 6.2 x 10.1 cm (Box 15)
      - Cisco
        - Snow sheds at summit station of the Central Pacific Railroad, Cisco, California, circa 1890; 9.9 x 16.2 cm on mount 10.7 x 16.4 cm (Box 15)
      - Concord
        - Group of cowboys, probably castrating steers, on the Bert Elsworthy Ranch, Concord, California, 1895 Jul 11; 20.4 x 25.3 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
          Names of ranch hands listed on verso, including Buck Mitchell, Bert Elsworthy, Edd Randall, Jacinto Soto, Pete Pacheco, and Telano Soto
      - East Biggs
        - Tractor pulling wagons loaded with 25 tons of peaches from the Hatch & Rock Orchard in Rio Bonito (later known as East Biggs), California, circa 1900-1905; 11.7 x 19.7 cm on mount 17.7 x 22.7 cm (Box 15)
          Caption in negative: Hatch and Roch's Fruit Train, 25 tons peaches from Rio Bonito Orchards
      - Jackson
        - Informal portrait of thirteen men preparing to go down Kennedy Mine, Jackson, California, circa 1890; 11.3 x 18.4 cm on mount 13.6 x 21.5 cm (Box 15)
      - Long Beach
        - View of the Pike, an amusement zone adjacent to the Long Beach Municipal Pier in Long Beach, California, circa 1904; 12.6 x 17.6 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
          Purchased from Michael Vinson on the William Robertson Coe Fund No. 3, 2010
      - Los Angeles
        - View of an oil field east from 1st Street and Belmont Avenue in Los Angeles, California, circa 1895; 14.4 x 22.6 cm on mount 22.1 x 29.6 cm (Box 15)
          Image number 222
      - Mount Lowe
        - Horses and riders going up a bridle road on Mount Lowe, California, circa 1893; 23.9 x 19.0 cm on mount 23.9 x 20.3 cm (Box 15)
          Advertisement on verso for the Mount Lowe Railway Co., Pasadena, California
      - Nevada City
        - Deer Creek and Suspension Bridge, Nevada City, California, circa 1890; 11.3 x 19.3 cm on mount 13.2 x 21.4 cm (Box 15)
      - Oakland
        - View of C. Savoy Texaco Service, a service station at 3725 San Leandro Street, Oakland, California, circa 1975; 20.3 x 25.3 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
        - Informal portrait of six African American woman probably in Oakland, California, and related to the Mount Zion Spiritual Temples, circa 1965; 20.6 x 25.3 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
          Removed from Mount Zion Spiritual Temples (Oakland, Calif.), Souvenir Program: Twentieth Annual Congress (1965)
        - Informal portrait of eleven African American women and two African American men, probably in Oakland, California and related to the Mount Zion Spiritual Temples, circa 1965; 20.6 x 25.3 cm, unmounted (Box 15)
      - Pasadena
        - View of the orange groves of the Sierra Madre Villa Hotel, Pasadena, California, 1886-1894; 11.1 x 18.1 cm on mount 13.2 x 21.6 cm (Box 15)
          Advertisement on verso for the Sierra Madre Villa Hotel
      - Santa Barbara
        - View of the cloister of the Mission Santa Barbara in Santa Barbara, California, circa 1890; 11.3 x 18.7 cm on mount 13.3 x 21.7 cm (Box 15)
          Image number 6619
        - View of a sacristy door of the Mission Santa Barbara in Santa Barbara, California, circa 1890; 18.3 x 11.3 cm on mount 21.7 x 13.4 cm (Box 15)
          Image number 6622A
      - Tustin
        - Fourth Street, Tustin, California, circa 1894; 11.2 x 18.6 cm on mount 13.3 x 21.5 cm (Box 15)
          Manuscript inscription on verso describes a walk through Tustin
          Image number 850
      - Unidentified locations in California
        - A wagon of the pulled by a team of horses under an oak tree covered with mistletoe, circa 1894; 12.7 x 20.6 cm on mount 13.2 x 21.5 cm (Box 15)
          Manuscript inscription by a tourist on verso: "Under the Mistletoe," and "showing the immense spread of the oaks and the mistletoe with which they are really all laden"
          Image number 214
        - A large log pulled by a team of oxen on a corduroy road at a logging site, circa 1885; 11.2 x 19.1 cm on mount 17.9 x 25.1 cm (Box 15)
          Printed below the photographic print on the recto: Made with the Cramer Extra Rapid Dry Plate. Sam C. Partridge, 529 Commercial Street, San Francisco, Agent for Pacific Coast. By an Amateur
    - Colorado
      - Colorado Springs
        - View of the Pyramid rock formation in North Cheyenne Canyon Park, Colorado Springs, Colorado, circa 1885-1890; 18.7 x 11.2 cm on mount 21.6 x 13.3 cm (Box 16)
      - Fort Garland
        - Bird's-eye view of Fort Garland, Colorado, looking south, 1882; 10.7 x 18.4 cm on mount 11.4 x 19.1 cm (Box 16)
      - Garden of the Gods
        - Rock formations, Garden of the Gods, Colorado, circa 1866; 9.1 x 5.4 cm on mount 10.2 x 6.1 cm (Box 16)
        - View of Pikes Peak through the Keyhole, a sandstone arch which connects the Siamese Twins rock formations in the Garden of the Gods, Colorado., circa 1880; 11.3 x 18.6 cm on mount 13.3 x 21.6 cm (Box 16)
        - Gateway to the Garden of the Gods, Colorado, showing Gate Rock, circa 1885; 11.2 x 18.7 cm on mount 12.6 x 20.3 cm (Box 16)
        - Gateway to the Garden of the Gods, Colorado, 1886; 10.9 x 19.4 cm on mount 13.4 x 21.4 cm (Box 16)
          Ink inscription on the verso, "A. M. Giddings, 1886"
        - Mushroom Pass, Garden of the Gods, Colorado, 1886; 11.2 x 19.7 cm on mount 13.4 x 21.4 cm (Box 16)
      - Georgetown
        - Georgetown, Colorado. High bridge in distance, Colorado Central Railroad, circa 1880-1890; 11.1 x 18.6 cm on mount 12.7 x 20.3 cm (Box 16)
          Image number 24
      - Manitou Springs
        - View of Manitou Springs, Colorado, looking southwest, circa 1886; 10.7 x 18.5 cm on mount 12.8 x 19.8 cm (Box 16)
      - Morrison
        - View of Morrison, Colorado, circa 1870; 10.0 x 16.1 cm on mount 10.8 x 16.5 cm (Box 16)
      - Nevada City
        - View of Nevada City, Colorado, 1863; 10.3 x 13.0 cm on mount 12.7 x 15.5 cm (Box 16)
      - Ouray
        - View southeast over Ouray, Colorado, circa 1890; 11.6 x 19.1 cm on mount 12.7 x 20.3 cm (Box 16)
      - Pagosa Springs
        - People standing and sitting around the perimeter of Big Pagosa Spring in Pagosa Springs, Colorado, circa 1880; 8.4 x 16.9 cm on mount 8.6 x 17.6 cm (Box 16)
      - Pike's Peak
        - Pike's Peak, Colorado, 1886; 10.7 x 19.7 cm on mount 13.4 x 21.4 cm (Box 16)
      - Silver Plume
        - View of Silver Plume, Colorado, circa 1890; 11.3 x 18.5 cm on mount 12.7 x 20.4 cm (Box 16)
      - Silverton
        - View of Silverton, Colorado, looking west, circa 1880; 11.5 x 19.7 cm on mount 12.5 x 20.2 cm (Box 16)
      - Williams Canyon
        - View of rock formation identified as the amphitheater in Williams Canyon, El Paso County, Colorado, circa 1880; 11.3 x 19.1 cm on mount 13.3 x 21.6 cm (Box 16)
      - Unidentified locations in Colorado
        - Series of photographs that depict clearing sagebrush in Colorado, circa 1890-1900; 3 photographic prints, 11.5 x 19.3 cmon mounts 12.7 x 20.2 cm (Box 16)
          Titles inscribed in the negatives: Morning (The Start); Noon (Half Day Work); and Night (Burning Brush)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 11.4 x 19.1 cm on mount 20.4 x 25.3 cm (Box 16)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 11.5 x 19.3 cm on mount 12.6 x 19.6 cm (Box 16)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 11.5 x 19.3 cm on mount 12.6 x 19.6 cm (Box 16)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 11.5 x 19.3 cm on mount 12.6 x 19.6 cm (Box 16)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 15.5 x 20.4 cm on mount 21.6 x 26.8 cm (Box 16)
        - View of a town in Colorado, circa 1895; 15.5 x 20.4 cm on mount 22.5 x 27.8 cm, hand-colored (Box 16)
    - Idaho
      - Coeur d'Alene Lake
        - St. Joe Hotel, Coeur d'Alene Lake, Idaho, circa 1895; 20.4 x 25.5 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Eagle
        - Colfax Eating House, Eagle City, Idaho, circa 1884; 9.0 x 11.7 cm on mount 10.8 x 13.3 cm (Box 17)
          Inscription on verso: "Bacon and Beans $1, 1884. Near the place where Danny Ferguson killed Steele." Reference to the death of Thomas Steele by Danny Ferguson, a partner of Wyatt Earp, on June 19, 1884
      - Gibbons Canyon
        - Summit of Gibbons Canyon, Idaho, circa 1900; 9.7 x 10.3 cm on mount 11.1 x 11.5 cm (Box 17)
          Inscription on verso: "Gibbon Pass - should be Clark's Pass"
      - Idaho City
        - Copy photograph of a parade passing in front of the Luna House hotel in Idaho City, Idaho, circa 1890-1900; 11.3 x 17.7 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
          The image depicts parade floats, possibly celebrating July 4th holiday. Accompanied by an envelope from Ballou-Latimer Pharmacy, Boise, Idaho, with undeveloped negatives of a town, mines, and the office of the Idaho World newspaper
      - Lapwai
        - Two Nez Perce Indian girls, Nez Perce Indian Reservation, Lapwai, Idaho, circa 1870; 5.5 x 8.1 cm on mount 6.2 x 10.0 cm (Box 17)
      - Lewiston
        - Northern Pacific Railroad locomotive number 673, train number 310, at the Lewiston Depot, Lewiston, Idaho, circa 1900; 12.7 x 16.6 cm on mount 17.8 x 22.8 cm (Box 17)
      - Pierce
        - Back view of the first courthouse and jail in Pierce City, Idaho, circa 1920-1930; 7.0 x 11.5 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Spalding
        - Ruins of the Lapwai Mission house, Spalding, Idaho, circa 1940; 8.8 x 14.8 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
          Letterpress caption on verso describes the Mission
        - Plaque marking the Lapwai Mission house site, Spalding, Idaho, circa 1940; 14.8 x 8.8 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
        - Fence bounding the Lapwai Mission house site, Spalding, Idaho, circa 1940; 8.0 x 13.0 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Trude
        - A view of Mount Sawtelle from North Fork Club, Trude, Idaho, circa 1900-1910; 8.1 x 10.7 cm on mount 15.9 x 16.2 cm (Box 17)
      - Wallace
        - Storefronts in Wallace, Idaho, circa 1880-1890; 12.2 x 18.2 cm on mount 12.6 x 20.4 cm (Box 17)
        - View of a mine at Wallace, Idaho, circa 1890-1900; 12.0 x 19.2 cm on mount 17.4 x 25.5 cm (Box 17)
    - Iowa
      - Davenport
        - View of the residence of James Monroe Parker (born 1823), Davenport, Iowa, circa 1890; 10.5 x 16.2 cm on mount 10.8 x 16.5 (Box 17)
          Manuscript inscription on verso states that Parker was a founder of Florence, Nebraska. In 1860, he managed the Bank of Florence
      - Spencer
        - Man posed standing behind agricultural machinery, identified as a Maurer's Special Baling Press, manufactured by the F. X. Maurer Company in Spencer, Iowa, circa 1890-1895; 19.8 x 24.2 cm on mount 22.2 x 28.6 cm (Box 17)
      - Spirit Lake
        - Children, women, and men posed standing in front of the Chase House in Spirit Lake, Iowa, circa 1885; 18.5 x 22.9 cm on mount 20.2 x 25.4 cm (Box 17)
    - Kansas
      - Argentine
        - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad yard in Argentine, Kansas, 1893; 11.6 x 16.2 cm on mount 16.6 x 21.1 cm (Box 17)
      - Deerfield
        - Group of about fifty men and a woman posed in front of train cars for the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad for a land excursion organized by the D. H. Bane & Co. real estate agency of Deerfield, Kansas, 1906 Jun 7; 19.2 x 24.1 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
          Inscription in the negatives: "D. H. Bane & Co." on the railroad cars
      - Emporia
        - Wreck on the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad, three miles east of Emporia, Kansas, 1897 Sep; 8.9 x 11.9 cm on mount 14.0 x 16.5 cm (Box 17)
          The accident killed fifteen people and wounded twenty-five. Passengers included William Jennings Bryan, who was en route to address a county fair at Burlingame, Kansas
      - Kechi
        - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad depot at Kechi, Kansas, including the station agent, circa 1900; 13.0 x 17.8 cm on mount 20.3 x 25.3 cm (Box 17)
      - Langdon
        - Exterior portrait of Benedict Shaffer (born 1828), Mary Shaffer (born 1827), and their dog posed standing in front of their cabin in Langdon, Kansas, 1876; 9.8 x 12.5 cm on mount 10.8 x 13.9 cm (Box 17)
      - Paola
        - View of the Sinkey building, northwest corner of the town square, Paola, Kansas, circa 1890; 14.4 x 20.8 cm on mount 14.4 x 20.8 cm (Box 17)
      - Turner
        - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad depot in Turner, Kansas, 1892; 9.4 x 12.0 cm on mount 14.1 x 16.4 cm (Box 17)
    - Minnesota
      - Brainerd
        - Wreck of the Northern Pacific Railroad bridge across the Mississippi River near Brainerd, Minnesota, 1875 Jul 28; 11.5 x 18.4 cm on mount 18.7 x 24.4 cm (Box 17)
        - Wreck of Northern Pacific Railroad locomotive number 723, which occurred in front of the Northern Pacific Hospital in Brainerd, Minnesota, 1882; 11.8 x 19.8 cm on mount 15.7 x 25.4 cm (Box 17)
        - Buildings in Brainerd, Minnesota, and a signal station in the distance, circa 1900; 8.8 x 8.9 cm, unmounted snapshot (Box 17)
        - Log piles and houses in Brainerd, Minnesota, circa 1900; 8.8 x 8.9 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
        - House in Brainerd, Minnesota, circa 1900 (Box 17)
      - International Falls
        - Informal portrait of an elderly Ojibwa Indian man, identified as Tee Ta Pa Shwe Witan, also known as Far Away Echo (born circa 1871), posed sitting in a canoe near Rainy Lake and International Falls, Minnesota, circa 1951; 10.7 x 14.0 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Lake City
        - Landing and warehouses in Lake City, Minnesota, circa 1870; 5.5 x 9.5 cm on mount 6.1 x 10.1 cm (Box 17)
        - Maiden Rock, five miles distance from Lake City, Minnesota, circa 1870; 5.5 x 9.4 cm on mount 6.1 x 10.1 cm (Box 17)
      - Minneapolis
        - Stores and the Pence Opera House, seen from the top of the Nicollet House, Hennepin Avenue between Washington Avenue and Second Street, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1868; 15.4 x 21.4 cm on mount 23.2 x 29.1 cm (Box 17)
      - Red Wing
        - Red Wing, Minnesota, from summit of Barn Bluff, circa 1870; 5.6 x 9.7 cm on mount 6.2 x 10.0 cm (Box 17)
      - Rock Creek
        - Engineers camp, Rock Creek, probably Minnesota, 1892 May; 20.0 x 25.4 cm, unmounted cyanotype (Box 17)
    - Montana
      - Alder Gulch
        - Overview of Alder Gulch, Montana, circa 1870; 5.6 x 9.7 cm on mount 6.2 x 10.0 cm (Box 17)
      - Belgrade
        - View of a stable, hardware store, and post office in Belgrade, Montana, circa 1885; 15.5 x 21.0 cm on mount 20.3 x 25.4 cm (Box 17)
      - Billings
        - Grand Hotel in Billings, Montana, includes proprietor George Fritz Benninghoff (1851-1926), second from left, circa 1887; 9.9 x 13.9 cm on mount 10.8 x 16.5 cm (Box 17)
          Manuscript inscription on verso: "Benninghoff second from post, bartender in apron"
      - Boulder
        - Northern Pacific Railroad locomotive number 484 Elkhorn engine on "Y" at Boulder, Montana, 1900; 12.1 x 17.0 cm on mount 12.4 x 18.1 cm (Box 17)
          Typed caption on verso states that engine is "one of the early Mogul type" and identifies the engineer and fireman
      - Butte
        - Corner of Main and Broadway, Butte, Montana, circa 1895; 9.5 x 12 cm on mount 13.4 x 15.7 cm (Box 17)
        - Exterior group portrait of the 1st Montana Volunteer Infantry, probably in Butte, Montana, 1899 Oct; 9.4 x 11.8 cm on mount 10.7 x 13.2 cm (Box 17)
          Sole regiment from that Montana to take part in the Spanish American War. The unit mustered in at Helena, Montana on May 5-10, 1898, mustered out at San Francisco, California on October 17, 1899, awarded service medals in Butte, Montana, October 23, 1899
      - Glendive
        - Depot for the Northern Pacific Railroad in Glendive, Montana, with several men posed in doorways and windows, 1890; 11.7 x 19.6 cm on mount 12.5 x 20.1 cm (Box 17)
          Manuscript inscription on verso identifies the dispatcher posed sitting in a window as F. E. Potter
      - Helena
        - Henry Siegel & Company building, along Jackson Street, Helena, Montana, circa 1864-1869; 5.5 x 9.5 cm on mount 6.1 x 10.1 cm (Box 17)
      - Hyalite Peak
        - Mount Hyolite (sic), 10,000 feet high, near Bozeman, Montana, circa 1890-1900; 12.9 x 18.0 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Lame Deer Creek
        - Northern Cheyenne Indian camp, showing summer arbor and meat drying in the sun, Lame Deer Creek, Montana, circa 1896; 9.8 x 12.5 cm on mount 10.8 x 13.2 cm (Box 17)
          Image number 206
      - Maiden
        - Copy photograph of oxen and wagons processing down a street in Maiden, Montana, identified as one of the last bull teams, 1884; 11.2 x 16.5 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Milk River
        - Assiniboine Indian child near the Milk River, Montana, 1896; 12.5 x 9.8 cm on mount 13.3 x 10.8 cm (Box 17)
      - Missoula
        - On a snowbound Grant Creek near Missoula, Montana, circa 1890-1900; 17.5 x 11.6 cm on mount 21.5 x 16.4 cm (Box 17)
      - Polson
        - Flathead Indian Agency, Montana, possibly showing the community of Polson, Montana, circa 1885; 12.2 x 17 cm on mount 13.2 x 18.3 cm (Box 17)
      - Pompey's Pillar
        - Pompey's Pillar, Montana, from the south, circa 1890-1900; 15.1 x 20.2 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
        - Down the river from the top of Pompey's Pillar, Montana, circa 1890-1900; 15.1 x 20.2 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Rocky Canyon
        - Northern Pacific Railroad in Rocky Canyon, five miles east of Bozeman, Montana, circa 1890; 12.9 x 18.0 cm, unmounted (Box 17)
      - Virginia City
        - Southeast corner of Burn and Wallace streets, Virginia City, Montana, circa 1870; 5.5 x 9.3 cm on mount 6.1 x 10.1 cm (Box 17)
      - Unidentified location
        - Frontier home, probably Montana, circa 1875; 11.7 x 19.0 cm on mount 12.8 x 19.7 cm (Box 17)
    - Nebraska
      - Fairbury
        - Nebraska National Guard, 2nd Regiment, Company D, in Fairbury, Nebraska, circa 1895; 19.3 x 24.1 cm on mount 19.3 x 24.1 cm (Box 18)
      - Ough
        - Farmworkers with haystacks and combing equipment in Ough, Nebraska, circa 1895; 12.1 x 17.2 cm on mount 20.3 x 25.4 cm (Box 18)
        - Geese and cattle on a farm, Ough, Nebraska, circa 1895; 12.3 x 17.2 cm on mount 20.3 x 25.4 cm (Box 18)
      - Trenton
        - Exterior portrait of Charles R. Nordin (born 1878) and his son, Charles R. Nordin, Jr. (born 1922), with four American Indian men at the dedication of the Massacre Canyon Monument, Trenton, Nebraska, 1930 Sep 26; 17.7 x 28.5 cm, unmounted (Box 18)
          The group is posed standing in front of a banner for "Western Historical Museum, Doc Carver's World Famous 100,000 Saddle & Bridle. Charles R. Nordin, Manager." Dr. William Frank Carver (1840-1927) was a Nebraska pioneer, exhibition shooter, and dentist
      - Unidentified locations
        - View of a man, woman and child in front of a sod house on the Great Plains, probably Nebraska, circa 1880-1890; 10.4 x 19.9 cm on mount 13.1 x 21.5 cm (Box 18)
        - Exterior portrait of Chief Little Dog, a Ponca Indian, probably in Nebraska, circa 1900; 19.5 x 12.6 cm on mount 19.5 x 12.6 cm (Box 18)
    - Nevada
      - Elko
        - Football team, Elko, Nevada, probably for a mining camp school; coach and fourteen players, including an African American boy, 1916; 13.0 x 17.9 cm on mount 19.7 x 24.8 cm (Box 18)
      - Carson City
        - Lumberyard at Carson City, Nevada, circa 1870; 9.3 x 15.3 cm on mount 11.5 x 18.5 cm (Box 18)
      - Schurz
        - Paiute Indians playing poker under the cottonwood trees at Walker River Indian Reservation in Schurz, Nevada, 1908; 9.1 x 14.7 cm, unmounted (Box 18)
      - Virginia City
        - Shaft in the Belcher Mine with cages containing ore in Virginia City, Nevada, circa 1875-1880; 9.3 x 15.4 cm on mount 11.6 x 18.5 cm (Box 18)
        - Party of men and women holding lanterns and preparing to descend into the Savage Mine of the California and Consolidated Virginia mines, Virginia City, Nevada., 1879 Oct 28; 19.1 x 24.6 cm, unmounted (Box 18)